Hannah Kim

Korean Name: Soyeon Kim

I am a hardworking individual that aims to provide my best work possible. I have strong organisational and time management skills that have been developed from my previous work experience. I have experience as a waitress at multiple different companies ranging from cafe's to restaurants, where I developed skills such as customer service, communication time management and teamwork. I have experience working at Berrysweet Strawberry farm where I picked strawberries / raspberries / blackberries in a team-orientated, fast pace environment while inspecting fruit for disease. I am also a person that aims to have a healthy body and mind by frequently going to the gym.

Personal Info

Phone

0434 400 656

E-mail

haikyu5123@gmail.com

Place of birth

Republic of Korea

Date of birth

1994-02-23

Skills

Healthy Body

Time Management

Organisational Skills

Problem Solving

Teamwork

Languages

Korean

English

Interests

Gym

Swimming

Experience

2020-05 - Team Lead Sushi Maker

present

Super Tetsudo

In a fast pace environment, It was my responsibility make quality sushi as efficiently as possible, while also managing the sushi team consisting of 3 people. My responsibilities included:

- Quality Control
- Controlling Flow
- Teaching Techniques

2019-07 - Waitress (Australia)

2019-09 *Tong 86*

In this position I learned how to efficiently and effectively, manage orders, tables and people in order to get orders out as fast as possible. The main tasks involved serving food, alcohol and cleaning the store.

2018-06 - Barista

2019-06 Starbucks

As a barista I had to prepare coffee and other beverages for customers quickly and effectively. Maintain a professional appearance while delivering excellent customer service.

service.

2020-02 - Grape Picking (Australia)

2020-03 Vinepower

This role required a consistent strong commitment to get work as the pickers were chosen through a first come first serve approach. I had to work extremely fast as work wasn't paid by the hour but by weight. I built strong teamwork skill and communication skills as picking for a farm was done as a team effort.

2019-09 - Strawberry/Raspberry/Blackberry Picker (Australia)

2019-12 Berrysweet Strawberry Farm

In this role I learned how to work in a fast pace environment while picking high quality fruit. I gained lots of teamwork experience as I was constantly part of a team that worked together to pick many rows of fruit. Other parts of this role included Inspecting fruit for disease and insects, and proper picking technique to avoid damaging the fruit as I'm picking.

Education

2013-03 - Sangi University

2017-02 Major: Bachelors of Commerce - International Trade

2010-03 - Poong Moon Girls Highschool

2013-02

Certificates

2019-07 Working Holiday Visa Expires: 01/07/2021

2019-08 RSA